

GUSTAVO MOURA FERREIRA AMORIM

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+55 (47) 99604-1366

gu.amorim@yahoo.com.br

Brusque, SC - Brazil

LinkedIn: guamorim https://linkedin.com/in/guamorim

GitHub: gu-amorim https://github.com/gu-amorim

Portfolio:

https://gu-amorim.github.io

ID Lattes: 8501067789255885 https://lattes.cnpq.br/8501067789255885

Skills

Development Languages

- C++
- C#
- Python
 - + Django and Django REST Framework
- JavaScript
 - + ReactJS and React Native
- TypeScript
- HTML
- · CSS
- MySQL

Operating Systems

- Windows
- MacOS
- Linux

Summary

Passionate Software Developer with over 1.5 years of experience in developing web, mobile applications, and backend APIs. Specialized in writing clear, concise and maintainable code. Experienced in collaborating with teams of various sizes across multiple projects. Highly adaptable, capable of working independently, remotely, or in office environments as needed.

Professional Experience

Aug. 2021 - June 2022 Fullstack Developer

Fullstack Developer (Web, IOS and Android)

Leader Aplicativos Brusque, SC - Brazil

- Developed web and mobile (IOS and Android) applications using JavaScript, React and React Native.
- Created web and mobile applications for new projects and resolved issues in existing ones.
- Collaborated with small and large teams across multiple projects.
- Identified design flaws in projects and provided solutions to ensure smooth roll-out of the final products.
- Experience as DevOps, deploying web and mobile applications, and managed Linux servers for backend APIs on AWS.

Jan. 2021 - Aug. 2021 Jr. Backend Developer

Backend Developer

Leader Aplicativos Brusque, SC - Brazil

- Developed APIs using Python, Django and Django Rest Framework (DRF).
- Created APIs for new projects and resolved issues in existing ones.
- Contributed to the backend development of an internal company project.
- · Worked on new clients projects with various teams.
- · Resolved issues in pre-existing projects.

Education

2019 - 2023

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science University of Vale do Itajaí - UNIVALI

Itajaí, SC - Brazil

2016 - 2020

English Course (Pre-intermediate to Advanced II)

Big Ben Languages School

Brusque SC - Brazil

Jan. 2018 - Feb. 2018

Advanced English Course Kensington Academy of English

London, United Kingdom